{
    "subject": "David_Dhawan",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Taaqatwar",
    "human_readable": "David Dhawan created Taaqatwar.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8018789291381836,
            "question": "Who created the movie Taaqatwar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6071341633796692,
            "question": "What year was Taaqatwar released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5845853686332703,
            "question": "What themes are explored in Taaqatwar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5318081378936768,
            "question": "Was Taaqatwar a successful movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4358457326889038,
            "question": "Who starred in the movie Taaqatwar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4165469706058502,
            "question": "Are there any awards associated with Taaqatwar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37930288910865784,
            "question": "What genre is the movie Taaqatwar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3262990713119507,
            "question": "Is David Dhawan known for directing action movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24730005860328674,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie directed by David Dhawan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23350626230239868,
            "question": "Can you name another movie directed by David Dhawan?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=David Dhawan created Taaqatwar.",
            "html": "yago_10546_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the movie directed by David Dhawan?",
            "html": "yago_10546_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is David Dhawan known for directing action movies?",
            "html": "yago_10546_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the movie Taaqatwar?",
            "html": "yago_10546_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10546_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10546_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10546_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10546_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10546_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10546_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10546_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10546_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10546_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10546_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide clear information that David Dhawan directed the film \"Taaqatwar,\" which was released in 1989. Therefore, the statement \"David Dhawan created Taaqatwar\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}